洪福飯店  我的最愛
Ah, Hop Foo's, my favorite.
來個早午餐也不錯
Don't mind if I brunch.
翻譯：Providence 持久君 兮之 MythCreator
翻譯： 扭扭扭布~V~ 麥田守望者
你連早餐都吃外賣嗎
Are you eating takeout for breakfast?
你現在可是我女朋友了
Hey, you're my girlfriend now.
時間軸：chance-coco 糖不甩   后期：MythCreator
你不應該對我的行為有異議
You're not supposed to judge anything I do.
你再說一遍
Say that again.
你現在是我女朋友了
You're my girlfriend now.
校對：丟丟曳       總監:  丟丟曳
我喜歡
I like it.
盡管你嘴里還有個餃子
Even when you have dumpling in your mouth.
但我還是喜歡
Sounds good.
我得走了  我今天
I have to go. I have a big meeting
-跟福斯特校長有個會  -我討厭那人
- with Principal Foster today. - I hate that guy.
-他總是否定你的想法  -不不不
- He always says no to your ideas. - No, no, no.
這次不會了  這次是
Not this one. This one is, uh,
保護海洋日的活動
Ocean Conservation Day.
杰茜  你為什么這么對自己呢
Why do you do this to yourself, Jess?
你是在勸我不去爭取直接放棄嗎
So you're telling me to not even try?
我只是不想讓你去碰了壁
I just don't want you to be
再感到失望
disappointed when he says no.
或許你應該努力去
Look, maybe you should try
別那么努力
to try a little less.
我該怎么努力去不努力呢
How am I supposed to try to not try?
是個矛盾
That's a catch-22.
教練
Oh, hey, Coach.
我掉了個餃子
Oh, I dropped a dumpling!
-那是他的早餐嗎  -是的
- That is his breakfast? - Yeah.
多可愛啊
Isn't it cute?
他一點都不覺得羞愧
He's not even ashamed of it. Oh.
拿住了
I got it!
差點就跑掉了
It almost got away from me... Aah!
杰茜駕到 第三季 第八集
福斯特校長  這是我們
Look, Principal Foster, we have the chance
大放異彩的一次機會
to do something really great.
所有的經費都是捐贈來的
Everything's been donated.
我們只需要準備車費就行了
All we need are transportation costs.
得了吧
Come on!
車旅費是做任何事情
That's only the most expensive
最昂貴的經費了
part of doing anything!
你真是  對不起
You... I'm sorry.
我太魯莽了
That was rude.
我昨晚沒睡好
I slept very badly last night.
大半夜喝了杯印度拉茶
Had a chai tea very late.
有朋友從蒙特利爾來看我
Had friends in from Montreal.
有的孩子一直住在洛杉磯
Some of these kids have lived in L.A. their entire lives
卻從來沒去看過大海
and they've never even seen the ocean.
上個星期我讓他們
Last week I asked them to draw
把他們想象中的海洋畫出來
what they thought the ocean looked like.
他們畫了一堆這些東西
I got a lot of stuff like this.
那是個長了翅膀的面包圈么
Is that a bagel with wings?
-是的  -屌爆了
- Yes, sir, it is. - Extraordinary.
我可不能接受您不同意這次活動的提議
I'm afraid I'm not taking no for an answer.
你還真就得碰壁了
You're gonna have to take no for an answer
這事沒得商量
because that's just the way it is.
長了腿的鯊魚
Hmm, a shark with legs.
一點都不合邏輯
That's not even anatomically close to correct.
這就是個方塊啊
That's just a square, though.
讓他們重新畫吧
Have them start over.
太糟糕了
That's just terrible.
尼克
Nick?
我想跟你談談你的健康狀況
I want to talk to you about your fitness level.
-談什么  我的身體  -你上一次鍛煉身體是什么時候
- Of what? My body? - When's the last time you worked out?
我來告訴你
You know what? I'll tell you
他上一次鍛煉身體是什么時候吧
when the last time he worked out was.
是他在跟他爹的其他精子
It was the time that he battled his daddy's other dumb sperm
爭奪誰先到達他娘的卵子的時候
in order to make his way to his mama's dumb-ass egg.
你的幽默感有所提高啊親
Your burns are getting better, man.
-廢話太多  -好吧
- Just really long. - Okay.
我不需要鍛煉身體
Look, I don't need to work out.
我是個經典康尼島的壯漢
I'm old-fashioned, Coney Island fat-strong.
尼可拉斯  早餐就吃中餐啊
Ah, Nicholas. Chinese food for breakfast.
真是健康啊
See you're still a health nut.
你不是應該在工作么
Aren't you supposed to be at work?
我請假了
I'm rocking a PD-- personal day.
最后一天搬家
Yeah, last day of the move.
教練  看來你真是抓緊一切時間搬到我原來的房間啊
Coach, I see you've wasted no time moving into my old room.
我就是過來
Anyway, I just came over to, uh,
還鑰匙的
drop off my old key.
這是個歷史時刻嘍
Wow, so this is like a moment.
想最后再來看看這個地方
Looking to get some much-needed space from this place.
-你不就是搬到對門嘛  -也是
- You're right across the hall. - That's true.
無論你身在何方
Everywhere you go...
我們與你同在
there you are.
-什么  -說啥呢
- What? - What?
他的牛仔褲好緊啊
His jeans are so small.
他看上去像個小木偶
He looks like a little puppet.
還是個意大利手工制作
Like something some Italian whittled.
你就讓我訓練訓練你吧
Come on, man, just let me train you.
尼克  我覺得你是該鍛煉了
You know what, Nick? You should do it.
我倒希望教練也能訓練訓練我
I would love for Coach to train me,
但我昨天打球有點
but I kind of pushed it too hard
打得太猛了
at the court yesterday.
扣了個籃
Went in for a dunk.
結果落地把腳崴了
Landed sort of funny.
典型的溫斯頓
Typical Winston.
-沒錯  -你什么意思
- That's true. - What is that supposed to mean?
你總是脆弱異常
Because you're always too injured to play.
記得上次你因為心情不好就不打比賽了嗎
Remember when you sat out of the game because you were sad?
我那時還很冷
I was also cold.
尼克  我們就這么做
Nick. Let's do this.
看著我
Look at me.
你現在又談戀愛了
Now, you're in a new relationship,
想做回十五歲青少年不是那么容易的
which puts you at risk for gaining the boyfriend 15.
-這都不叫事兒  -這就是事兒
- That's not a thing. - It is a thing.
杰茜就喜歡我這樣的
Jess is into this.
我見過的例子數不勝數
I've seen this happen a million times.
十五歲的青春少年很快就成了二十歲的糙漢子
The boyfriend 15 quickly turns into the boyfriend 20.
接下來  你就成了個大胖子
Next thing you know, you're a fat dude on a little bike
戴著牛仔帽  騎著自行車  喊著”我屁股痛”
with a cowboy hat on talking about, "My ass hurts."
-我可不想變成那樣  -我也不想你變成那樣
- I don't want to be that. - I don't want you to be that.
我是會騎著車繞圈子
I would just be riding around in circles
-還是確實要去某個地方  -繞圈  伙計
- or would I be going places? - Circles, dude.
你就等著變成肥豬手吧
Fat-guy rash on your arm.
好吧  施密特想把我弄去鍛煉不是一天兩天了
Okay, look, Schmidt's tried to get me to work out for years.
他都沒成功
It didn't take.
而且  我背痛可嚴重了
Also, and it's not an excuse,
這可不是借口
I have a very bad back.
-你背痛嗎  -是啊
- Your bad back? - Yeah.
兩天前你一路上都背著我
You gave me a piggyback ride
還有說有笑的
two days ago and you giggled the whole time.
可棒了
It was awesome.
-還很有意思  -可有意思了
- It was also really funny. - That was pretty funny.
-我們還上了樓梯  伙計  -是啊
- We took the stairs, dude. - Yeah.
-那是因為我很興奮  -尼克
- It's 'cause I was excited. - Nick.
你要么吃了這個餃子做個大胖餃
Either take this dumpling and be a dumpling guy,
要么跟我鍛煉做個大壯男
or you train with me, and be a do-ing guy.
這可不容易  我這輩子都還是個大胖餃
It's hard because I've been a dumpling guy my whole life...
我知道
I know.
我只要你一天時間
One day, that's all I need.
然后改變你一生
And I will change your life.
你會看到自己的實力
You'll be able to see your abs.
我以為我生來無能
I thought God just didn't give me those.
來吧
Come on.
就這么做
Let's do it.
-好兄弟  -我加入
- My man! - I’m in!
我可得先警告你
I'm gonna warn you.
我可不是鍛煉的料
Working out is not my thing.
別擔心  兄弟  我從不失敗
Not worried, man. I do not fail.
我也加入
You know what? I'm in, too.
你受傷了  你不能去
You're injured, you shouldn't, you shouldn't do it.
什么  得了吧
What? Come on, Winny the Bish
貝小溫可不怕這點痛  寶貝兒
play through the pain, baby. You know what?
我們先來點開合跳熱熱身
Let's warm up with some jumping jacks.
我本來想...
I was going... Oh!
戴老師
Miss Day!
看看我這酷炫的沙灘帽
Check out my cool beach hat.
不幸的是  我有個壞消息
Unfortunately, um, I have some bad news.
我們不會去野外考察了
Uh, we're not gonna get to go on that field trip.
但是你說過一切皆有可能  戴老師
But you said anything is possible, Miss Day.
你就一直穿著那頂帽子吧  克里斯多
You just keep wearing that hat, Crystal.
因為只要熱狗能做帽子
Because as long as hot dogs are hats...
一切皆有可能
Anything is possible.
你可以是宇宙里第一個小女孩
You could be the first little girl in space.
騎著熱狗帽一路飛向月亮吧  姑娘
You just ride that hot dog hat all the way to the moon, girl.
克里斯多  你不準碰我
Oh, Crystal, you're not legally allowed to touch me.
但是謝謝你
But thank you.
猜猜看誰又有了教練
Hey, guess who got a trainer.
這么多菜單
So many menus.
我會跟貝瑞·邦茲[美國棒球運動員]一樣健壯
I'm gonna look like Barry Bonds.
搞什么
Seriously, what the hell?
我知道了  跟福斯特談得不怎么樣
I take it, it didn't go well with Foster.
-確實不怎么樣  -杰茜
- It did not go well. - Aw, Jess.
我不想看你這么受傷
I hate seeing you hurt like this.
你搞什么  更多的菜單
Are you serious? More menus?
這簡直
This is like...
我們干嘛要更多菜單
Why do we need more menus?
我們的菜單還不夠嗎
Don't we have enough menus?
感覺你說了好多個菜單
Feels like you're saying menus a lot.
這簡直是環保災難
This is an eco-disaster.
保守黨就該勝選
Conservation deserves a win today.
洪福飯店已經砍掉最后一顆樹了
Hop Foo's has killed its last tree.
杰茜  你現在散發著
Jess, this feels like
發生了什么事的氣場
a something-else-is-going-on type of thing.
你還能開車嗎  你眼睛都綠了
Are you okay to drive? You got crazy eye!
歡迎光臨洪福飯店  有什么能幫您的嗎
Uh, welcome to Hop Foo's. Can I help you?
今天早上  我公寓出現了九張你們的菜單
This morning, there were nine menus just in my apartment.
我也恨那些菜單  太不環保了
I also hate those menus, they're so bad for the environment.
這很浪費的
It's wasteful.
簡直是環保災難
It's an eco-disaster.
我會跟老板說說  看我們能不能改改
I'll talk to my boss, see if we can change that.
很好  你就那么做
Yeah, great, you do that.
我會追蹤你們怎么處理的
I'm gonna follow up with you on that.
我們堆肥  回收  但是
I compost, recycle, but it's...
我覺得還不夠
I don't feel like it's enough.
謝謝你  太謝謝你了
Thank you. Geez, thank you so much
能夠站出來  說出來
for stepping up and saying something.
我就是這樣  我
That's who I am, that's just, you know, I'm...
-我叫布萊恩  -杰茜  杰茜卡  杰茜
- My name's Brian. - Jess. Jessica. Jess.
能碰到真正在乎環保人感覺太好了
It's really refreshing to meet someone who actually cares.
也要歸功于你的魅力
Well, it helps that you're gorgeous.
不可能
No, that's crazy.
你逗我呢
That ain't real.
無語了
That's dumb.
真的無語了  你蠢死了
That's straight dumb. You're dumb.
你可好了
You're nice.
假期愉快嗎
You excited for the holidays?
我很愉快
I am.
好了
Anyway...
我這個方法本身設計得就很簡單
My system is built to be easy. Okay.
像花生一樣簡單
It's easy as peanuts.
-像花生一樣簡單  -是的
- Easy as peanuts? - Yeah.
沒有這種表達  沒有人這樣說
That's not an expression; no one says that.
"花生"是個縮略詞  "花生"表示
PEANUTS is an acronym. PEANUTS stands for:
瘋狂體育鍛煉活動
Physical Education Activity Nuts!
就是  嗨起來  好好玩這樣
Like, like go nuts, have fun!
是  但你得用到每個單詞的首字母啊
Yeah, but you got to use every letter.
我知道  但是這樣也可以
I'm aware of that, but it still works.
進展如何  伙計
What's going on, guys?
我們開始吧
Let's do this.
告訴你喲  沒有什么傷痛
I tell you, ain't no injury gonna hold
能阻礙貝小溫  因為我是個戰士
old Winnie the Bish down 'cause I'm a warrior.
尼克懂的
Nick knows.
做波比嗎[一種高強度無氧運動]
Burpee?
好的  沒關系
All right, cool.
你的傷會變嚴重的
Injury is gonna get worse.
我不是個半途而廢的人
I'm not a quitter!
施密特  怎么了  兄弟
Hey, Schmidt, what's going on, man?
一切都好嗎
Everything okay?
我奧克蘭突擊者隊的小帽子是不是落那邊了
Did I leave my Oakland Raiders yarmulke over there?
不知道  我和教練在鍛煉
Don't know. Coach and I are working out.
這么多年  我一直想讓你鍛煉
I've been trying to get you to work out for years.
過來吧  伙計
Well, just come over, man.
我很享受我自己的地盤
I'm enjoying my space.
也許你可以按一下擴音鍵
But maybe you should just put me on speaker.
好了  說吧
Okay, you're on.
好  介紹一下現在的情形吧
Okay, cool, set the scene.
那邊現在是什么狀況
What's the vibe over there?
尼克還穿著牛仔褲呢
Nick's in jeans.
尼克松牛仔褲
Nixon jeans?
尼克松牛仔褲是個什么鬼東西
What the hell are Nixon jeans?
不過聽起來很不錯的樣子
They sound really cool.
我把那個菜單的事情解決了
Hey, I solved the menu thing.
我直接沖過去然后采取了行動
I just went down there, I took action.
厲害吧
Boom-yah.
我做出改變了喲
I made a change.
因為我做到了  我真的覺得
Now that I can do that, I really feel
我能搞定這個野外考察的事情
like I can figure out this field trip thing.
更厲害了吧
Double boom.
我們還有一些事情沒解決
There are still some things we need to figure out.
得讓他們明白我們的想法
Just got to get the message across.
你不用再給我們發這個了
Hey, hey, you don't, you don't need to leave these anymore.
你要跑去哪兒
Where are you running to?
誰派你來的
Who sent you?
布萊恩  我還以為你要和你老板談談呢
Brian, I thought you were gonna talk to your boss.
我就是老板啊
I am the boss.
洪福飯店是你開的嗎
Hop Foo's is your restaurant?
抱歉我撒了謊
Sorry I lied.
你看起來有點抓狂  我不想和你打交道
You just seemed kind of crazy, so I didn't want to deal.
但是你很喜歡交流啊
But you care about conservation.
我不喜歡  真的一點也不
Oh, I don't, I really don't.
我只關心我的飯店
I care about my restaurant.
見鬼吧你  布萊恩
You're going down, Brian!
我要收集大家的簽名
I'm gonna collect signatures,
我還會寫一封請愿書
I'm gonna start a petition,
然后把它交給飯店的
and I will turn it in to the person
負責人
who's in charge of restaurants.
我會讓這整個城市都知道你
And I'm gonna report you to the city!
不  不要整個城市
Oh, no, not the city.
不
No!
你這個混蛋  布萊恩
You're a jerk, Brian!
我要把你的飯店燒成灰
I'm gonna burn down your building!
我不會那樣做的  我不會那樣做的
I won't do that, I won't do that.
為什么人們會這樣混蛋
Why do people suck?!
我們會先用一些音樂熱身
Okay, we're gonna warm up with music.
感覺到了嗎
Yeah, feeling that?
我猜是的
I guess so.
放松肩部
Yeah, got to loosen up the shoulders.
擺動雙臂
Wiggle those arms.
-手臂  不是臉  -抱歉
- Arms, not your face. - Oh, sorry,
我以為你說的是臉
thought you said "Face."
真性感  鍛煉很性感
Sexy. Working out is sexy.
這一點都不性感  兄弟
That's not sexy, man.
這才性感
This is sexy.
那一點也不性感
That isn't sexy.
真見鬼
Damn it!
這鍛煉的音樂真好聽
It's a great workout track!
感覺真棒
That was nice.
時間到
And time.
-太棒了  -太棒了
- Yes! - Yes!
再來一次
Let's do it again.
-再一次  -是啊  兄弟
- Again? - Yeah, man.
六  七  八
Six, seven, eight.
加油啊  兄弟
Come on, man!
我的壞了
Mine's broken.
搞定它  你可以的
Push through it, man, you got it.
-謝天謝地你來了  希希  -什么急事
- Ah, thank God you're here, Cece. - What's the emergency?
為什么杰茜需要這些中國菜
Why does Jess need all this Chinese food?
不  都是我編出來的
No, no, no, I just made all that up.
等等  你騙我給你買東西吃
Wait, you tricked me into getting you food?
是的
Yes.
為什么
Why?
-尼克  這是啥  -等下再說  別擔心
- Nick, what is this? - For after-- don't worry about it.
我馬上就回來
I will be right back.
你好啊
Hello.
-我是希希  我記得你  -是啊  記憶力真好
- I'm, I'm Cece, I-I remember you. - Yeah, yeah, yeah, great memory.
就是這樣  就是這樣
That's what's up, that's what's up.
毫無疑問
No doubt.
不能猶豫
Diggity.
尼克
Nick!
胸脯  尼克
Breasts-- Ni...
這是飯錢  零頭
This is for the food, and there's a little extra
歸你
for you.
老天  你要給我小費嗎
Oh, my god, are you tipping me?
沒錯
Yeah.
如果我以后經濟危機了  再還我
Well, if I'm gonna get in trouble, give it back.
我給了你四美元
I gave you four bucks.
我會給你很多小費  我現在就給你
I'll tip you good... I'll tip you right over.
尤物吧
Good stuff.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah.
可惡  我真希望我能說點別的
Damn, I wish I could have said something else.
-"現在就給你"就挺好  -好吧  她單身嗎
- "Tip you right over" was good. - Oh, okay, cool. Uh, is she single?
-是的  差不多吧  -太棒了伙計
- Yeah, kind of. - Oh, cool, man.
-是的  -你在做什么呢
- Yeah. - What are you doing?
我只是  不過是補充點蛋白質而已
Oh, I'm just gonna-- it's just a protein boost.
我就吃一點
I'm just gonna eat a little.
這可不行  伙計
That's not how it works, dude.
我們還在鍛煉中呢
We're still in the middle of our workout.
-還沒完嗎  -沒有
- We're not done yet? - No!
我剛才和餐館老板
I just had a very productive conversation
進行了一次富有建設性的談話
with the owner of the restaurant.
行動已被采納  改變即將發生
Action has been taken, change is in the air.
現在我要去我房間研究官司來找點樂趣了
Now I'm going to go research lawsuits in my room for fun.
你還好嗎
You okay?
-你看起來有心事  -別再去那個地方訂餐了
- You seem a little off. - Stop ordering from that place.
尼克  把餃子放下
Nick, put the dumpling down.
杰森·斯特里特  《勝利之光》中黑豹隊四分衛
感覺如何  杰森·斯特里特
Hey, what's up, Jason Street?
網上說我不該下地走路
The Internet said that I had to stay off my feet,
但之后我就發現了這把輪椅
but then I found this wheelchair in a ditch,
我準備好開始鍛煉了
so I'm ready to work out.
溫斯頓  去躺下  尼克  把餃子放下
Winston, go lay down. Nick, put the dumpling down.
放松
Relax.
你剛才喘粗氣了嗎
Did you just gasp?
-我要吃一個  -沒門
- I'm having one... - Down.
我再來一遍  別
I'm gonna ask you again. Don't...
別那么做
Don't do it.
別
Don't. D...
我要吃一口這個
I'm going to eat one bite of this.
別吃  你能做的更好
Don't do it. You're better than this.
我不知道  我也許
I don't know if I am. I might..
不  別  別
No. Don't, don't.
別再那么搖了
Stop shaking it like that.
-讓我把餃子吃了  -發生什么了
- Let me eat the dumpling! - What's going on?
剛剛鍛煉完
Oh, just working out.
是的  在休息而已
Yeah. Just chilling.
這個里面放味精了嗎
Does this food have MSG in it?
什么
What?
我的老天爺  味精會把我的下巴定住
Oh, my God, MSG makes my jaw lock up.
你沒事吧  伙計
You all right, dude?
什么
What? Mm-hmm.
-你的下巴怎么了  -是啊怎么了
- What's going on with your jaw? - Yeah, dude.
你個混蛋
Come on, you son of a...
等等
Wait a minute.
這里寫了"不含味精"
Ha, "No MSG."
你要去哪
Where are you going?
-我要帶溫斯頓一起出去溜溜  -你要帶我去哪
- I'm just taking Winston for a walk. - Where are you taking me?
我覺得他需要呼吸些新鮮空氣
I think he needs some fresh air.
可惡  教練
Damn it, Coach.
尼克  你給我認真想想下一步要做的事
Nick! I want you to really think about your next step.
你為什么這么關心
Why do you care so much?
這是重要關頭  你人生的十字路口
This is a crucial moment, a crossroads.
如果你吃了它  你就是在告訴我
By you eating that, you are telling me
你寧可坐在沙發上吃餃子
that you'd rather sit on the couch eating dumplings
也不愿意為你的生活做些事情
than do something with your life.
那么  你是個實干者還是個食餃者
Now, are you a doer or a dumpling-er?
抱歉  我不是你  兄弟
I'm sorry, I'm not you, man.
我是個食餃者
I'm a dumpling-er.
是全素的
Oh, it's veggie.
我做的全是無用功嗎
I did all that for nothing?
我已經嘗試了
I tried.
你要帶我去哪
Where are you taking me?
什么  你是我的小煙槍
What? You're my smoking gun.
溫斯頓坐輪椅了嗎
Winston's in a wheelchair?
意大利著名喜劇演員  奧斯卡影帝
下一步會怎樣  羅貝托·貝尼尼穿過長廊
What's next, Roberto Benigni coming through the halls,
讓所有人都發笑嗎
making everybody laugh?
什么都沒能參與到
Missing everything.
拿這個
Take these.
別說話
Don't even talk.
我朋友對你的食物過敏
My friend is having an allergic reaction to your food.
-你好  -菜單上
- Hey, man. - It says
寫著"不含味精"
"No MSG" on the menu.
另外還寫了
It also says it with the--
你管一個圓圈中有一條斜線的標志叫什么
what do you call the circle with the diagonal line?
-那是捉鬼敢死隊之類的標志  -什么
- It's the Ghostbusters thing. - What?
電影捉鬼敢死隊里的標志
From the movie Ghostbusters.
上面寫著那句話
Oh, it says it with words
還有捉鬼敢死隊的標志
and it says it with the Ghostbusters thing.
好了  冷靜點
All right, just calm down.
不  這就是接下來會發生的事
No, here's what's going to happen.
你要停止到處亂發這些菜單
You're going to stop putting these menus everywhere,
不然的話我就告訴別人
or I'm going to show the people
吃了這里的食物會變成什么樣
in here what happens when you eat the food.
我其實很喜歡這里的食物
I actually like the food.
聽我說  杰茜  中國的食物都含味精
Listen, Jess, Chinese food is MSG.
美國人生活在謊言中
America is living a lie,
而且我們發菜單人們才有餐可點
and we distribute menus so people order the food.
你就是要接受這些潛規則
Just accept that that's the way things are!
不  我受夠了接受這些潛規則
No, I am done accepting things the way they are,
因為到處都是這些菜單
because there are menus everywhere,
還有那些想要看大海的孩子們
and there are kids who want to see the ocean.
你在說什么
What?
還有我不喜歡你的氣場  伙計
And I don't like your vibe, dude.
這就是我朋友吃了這里東西的后果
This is what eating here did to my friend.
那個是炒干面嗎
Is that crispy noodles?
教練
Coach.
噢  不  不*
*Oh, no, no.
你在干什么  伙計
What the hell are you doing, man?
我在彈島嶼的節拍
I'm making Island Beats.
我覺得這就是從今以后我要做的事情
I think this is what I'm gonna do from now on,
因為顯然我做不了教練了
since, obviously, I can't coach.
我以為我們只是瞎鬧鬧
I thought we were just messing around.
為什么你把它變得這么復雜
Why are you taking this so hard?
因為  伙計  我想證明給自己看
Because, dude, I was trying to prove to myself
我還能做這些事
that I could still do this.
自從瑪莉亞和我分手后  不知怎么回事
Ever since Malia broke up with me-- I don't know--
我一團糟  感覺自己一無是處
I've just been a mess. Feel like I can't do anything right.
親們  一會能鎖上  一會又鎖不上了
Guys, it's locked, it's unlocked.
把它修好吧  說真的
Get it together for real.
你來這干什么
What are you doing here?
你不是說你忙得很嗎
I thought you said you were so busy.
我找到了一只多余的鬧鐘
I found this extra alarm clock,
我覺得這是表達鄰里友好的好禮物
and, uh, I thought it'd be neighborly,
所以我會幫你們放好
so I'll set it up for you guys.
別客氣
You're welcome.
等一下
Wait a second.
-那是什么  -什么是什么
- What is that? - What's what?
那是攝像頭嗎
Is that a camera?
斯密特  你在監視我們嗎
Schmidt, are you spying on us?
這是個...  這是個攝像頭
So... It is... it's a camera.
真雷到我了
Well, I'm shocked.
斯密特  是你決定要搬出去的
Schmidt, look, you decided to move out.
-那就搬走吧  -我已經搬走了
- So move out. - I am out.
其實我很忙的  知道嗎
I'm actually very busy, you know that?
事實上我已經遲到了
I'm actually late
我有一個很重要的咖啡約會是和...
for a very important coffee with a...
和我的一個好朋友
with a dear friend of mine.
誰呀
Who's that?
-是誰  -沒錯
- Who? - Yeah.
你想知道嗎
Wouldn't you like to know?
緊身褲小哥*
*Tiny pants man
他沒有朋友*
*He don't have friends
這就是為什么他買了那個鬧鐘*
*That's why he got the clock
他要用那個鬧鐘來觀察他僅有的朋友們*
*He got the clock to watch his only friends
你們用餐愉快嗎
Are you enjoying your meal?
溫斯頓吃的時候也很愉快  對吧
Winston enjoyed his meal, right?
-直到他過敏了  -我們走吧
- Until he had an allergic reaction. - Let's go.
看見沒  我趕走了你所有的客人
There. I drove away all of your customers,
而且我打算每天如此
and I'm gonna do that every day
直到你停止發菜單為止
until you stop with the menus.
-地球戰士  -你贏了  我不發了
- Earth warrior! - You win. I'll stop.
謝謝
Thank you.
查爾斯
Charles?
你被解雇了
You're fired.
-什么  -不  天哪  天哪
- What? No! - Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
-天哪  上帝啊  -你不能炒了他
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God! - Don't fire him.
他就是負責發菜單的
He's the menu guy.
我只是想有所改變
I was just trying to make a difference.
你做到了  今天早上這個人還有工作
You did. At the beginning of the day, this guy had a job.
現在他沒了  祝賀你勝利了  你贏了
Now he doesn't, so congrats on your victory. You win.
你有教書的經驗嗎
Do you have any teaching experience?
誰有抗組胺劑嗎[治療過敏的藥物]
Does anyone have an antihistamine?
知道嗎  我只是搬到了樓道的另一邊
You know, I just moved across the hall,
但感覺卻像是搬去了大洋彼岸
but it feels like I moved across an entire ocean.
人都會長大  尤其是年輕人
People grow up, especially young people.
所以我的朋友就一點都不想我嗎
So my friends don't even miss me anymore? Uh-huh.
他們不想你
Well, they don't miss you.
他們向前看了
They've moved on.
什么
What?
你怎么知道
Well, how do you know that?
因為是他告訴我的
Because he told me.
他叫康納  他去了賓漢姆大學
His name is Conner, and he went to SUNY Binghamton.
我以前和四十只鳥住在一起
I once lived with 40 birds,
后來它們都飛走了  我就向前看了
and they all flew away, and I moved on.
慢點吃面條  兄弟
Slow down on the noodles, buddy.
祝賀你  米勒  你是對的
Well, congratulations, Miller. You were right.
怎么了
What happened?
我恐嚇了一家餐館
I terrorized a restaurant.
我讓一個好人失業了
I got a good man fired.
我好像用輪椅碾死了一只蜥蜴
I might have ran over a lizard with my wheelchair,
我很愧疚
but I am ashamed of it.
這就是你努力的結果
So, that's what you get for trying.
讓我嘗嘗敵人的味道
Let's see what the enemy tastes like.
-美味啊  -誰能帶我去上個廁所
- It's good. - Anybody want to help me use the bathroom?
-不  -好吧  我自己來
- No. No. - Okay, I'll work it out.
我都不該嘗試的  結局就是受傷
I shouldn't have even tried. You just get hurt.
這真是種解脫啊
This is such a relief.
現在我可以變胖了
I can get fat now.
伙計們  停下來
Hey, guys, stop it!
我想一整天都吃這個東西
I want to eat this all day.
我們就像是中國食物粉絲團
Like a Chinese food menage. Oh!
你們都是實干者  而跟我一樣的人
Okay, you guys are doers, and people like me,
什么都不干的人
people who don't do anything--
事實上我們需要你們這樣的人
we actually need people like you.
天哪  這樣可不好
Oh, boy, this is bad.
好吧  就這么辦
Uh, this... Okay, all right.
我要給你們做段演講
I'm gonna give you guys a speech,
它會讓你們振作起來
and it's gonna fire you guys up.
-掉了一點兒在褲子上  -首先我們從贊美開始
- Got some on my pants... - First we're gonna start with compliments
來構建你們的信心
to build up your confidence. Okay, uh,
教練  你是位很棒的家伙
Coach, you're a great guy.
你身材很強壯
You've got strong bodies.
什么
What?
你只是需要更多的客戶  我相信你
You just need some more clients. I believe in you.
-謝謝  -杰茜  你棒極了
- Thanks. - Jess, you're awesome.
你是我目前遇到過的
You are the most resourceful,
最足智多謀  樂觀開朗
optimistic, amazing person
令人驚奇的人
I've ever met in my life.
我甚至沒法讓孩子們去野外考察
I can't even get my kids on a field trip.
你可以做你想做的任何事
You can do anything you put your mind to '
因為你狠聰明  知道嗎
cause you're smart, okay?
他們為什么沒法去野外考察
Why can't you get 'em on this field trip?
根本沒辦法讓他們去海灘
There's no way to get them to the beach.
那就是困難  客服它
That's a board. Karate-kick it!
你不經常給人做演講吧  是吧
You're not used to making speeches, are you?
關鍵一點就是  永不放棄
Point of it is, is you never give up.
好吧  我猜你們贏了
Fine. I guess you win.
我有點懷念在這里了
I sort of miss being here.
監視攝像頭可以撤了
Well, the nanny cam kind of gave it away.
由于沒人幫我
Well, nobody helped me,
-所以現在真是一團糟  -嗨  溫斯頓
- so now there is a real mess. - Hey, Winston,
你能借我們一點兒錢嗎
do you have some money where we could rent,
能夠租車或者租巴士之類的
like, a car or a bus or something?
我還是在溝里發現這個輪椅的呢
I found this wheelchair in a ditch.
有人能告訴我發生了什么嗎
Is anyone gonna tell me anything that's going on?
停  如果不是有關于租小車或者中型車的主意
Stop! If it's not an idea about how to rent a car or a van,
我就不想聽
then I don't want to hear it!
等一下  尼克
Wait a minute. Nick?
太聰明了
That's brilliant!
小伙伴們  交通工具是由
Boys and girls, transportation provided
洪福飯店提供的
by Hop Foo's restaurant.
好了  同學們  我們到了
All right, everybody, we did it!
海洋保護日  現在開始
Ocean Conservation Day starts... now!
歡迎來到太平洋
Welcome to the Pacific Ocean!
世界上最大的海洋就在我左邊
Yeah. The large body of water to my left.
不準胡鬧  孩子們  不要和陌生人說話
No horseplay, guys. Guys, don't talk to strangers.
你還說
And you said
-這不會合適  -我知道它很合適
- it wouldn't fit. - I knew it would fit.
我只是不想讓你把它帶來
I just didn't want you to bring it.
小心  輪子有點問題
Careful. It's got a trick wheel.
-沒事的  -好吧
- I think it's fine. - Okay.
-輪子掉了  -抱歉
- Aah! Trick wheel. - Not fine. Sorry.
這輪椅真不錯
Nice wheelchair.
戴女士
Ms. Day?
-你好  -謝謝你
- Hey. - Thank you.
給你  你應得的
Here. You deserve this.
謝謝你  我很喜歡
Oh, thank you. I love it.
但我覺得這個禮物應該屬于尼克·米勒
But you know what? I think this actually belongs to Nick Miller,
都是他的功勞
'cause he did this.
這位是你父親嗎
Is this your dad?
你覺得我是有多老  小姑娘
How old do you think I am, little girl?
好吧
All right.
我不想要這個禮物
I don't want this gift.
這是她最喜歡的帽子
It's her favorite hat.
你做出了改變  感覺怎么樣
You made a difference. How's it feel?
感覺棒極了
It feels good.
真的  感覺很好  我覺得像...
Yeah, actually, it feels great. I feel like, um...
我覺得像在跑步
I don't know. I feel like running.
教練  你想教我嗎
Hey, Coach, you want to show me how?
-教你怎么跑  -來吧  教教我
- How to run? - Come on. Coach me!
這樣對嗎  教練  我做得對嗎
Is this right, Coach? Am I doing it right?
米勒  你是人類的奇葩
Miller, you sorry excuse for a human being,
你就像豆袋椅一樣
you are shaped like a bean bag chair!
我要坐死你
I will sit in you!
-你能行的  -我也要來
- Ah, you can do it. - I'm coming, too.
因為我不會放棄  輪椅神探來了
'Cause I ain't a quitter! Ironside!
我來了  我來...
I'm coming. I'm com...
我是沙灘形的
I am all-terrain, baby.
我以前看錯你了  好嗎  你不是一個隨便放棄的人
I was wrong about you, okay? You're not a quitter.
現在請放棄
Now, please, quit!
我很高興看到這些
I'm glad I got to see that.
施密特
Oh, Schmidt,
把鑰匙還給你
here's your key back.
我們喜歡你在身邊
We kind of like having you around.
謝謝
Thanks.
不過這只是個備用的
This is just a copy, though.
我有差不多五十把放在家呢
I have, like, 50 of them at home.
他們要對我干嘛
What are y'all doing to me?
你的學生們在掩埋溫斯頓呢
Your students are burying Winston.
他喜歡這樣
Ah, he likes it.
離我遠點  聽著  你爸媽在哪兒
Get away from me! Look, where your parents at?
讓開  熊孩子們
Shoo, children! Shoo!
走開
Away now! Away... be away!
-一邊去  -看我一身沙
- Shoo. Get out of here. - All the sand!
-閉嘴  溫斯頓  -我是家人
- Shut up, Winston! - I'm family!
你不能這樣對我  你太壞了  你在干嘛
You can't do this to me! You're so mean! What are you doing?
-這是報應  -可憐的溫斯頓
- This is karma. - Oh, Winston.